Guide to The Adrian Flannelly Show Audio Recordings AIA.089
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: The Adrian Flannelly Show, 1976-2001; 256 audiocassettes in 4 flatboxes
  - October 7, 2000, cuid43540 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0242)
  - October 14, 2000, cuid43541 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0243)
  - October 28, 2000, cuid43542 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0244)
  - November 4, 2000, cuid43543 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0245)
  - November 11, 2000, cuid43544 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0246)
    Duration: 60 minutes; Preservation Note: Side 2 is blank.
  - November 11, 2000, cuid43545 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0247)
  - November 18, 2000, cuid43547 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0249)
    Duration: 14 minutes
  - November 25, 2000, cuid43548 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0250)
  - December 2, 2000, cuid43549 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0251)
  - December 9, 2000, cuid43550 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0252)
  - December 16, 2000, cuid43551 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0253)
  - December 30, 2000 - Part 1, cuid43586 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0288)
    This episode features historian Dr. James Murphy discussing the Great Famine. The episode also includes "12 Days of Christmas" music.
  - December 30, 2000 - Part 2, cuid43587 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0289)
    This episode features author Malachy McCourt.
  - December 30, 2000 - Part 3, cuid43588 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0290)
  - January 6, 2001 - Part 1, cuid43589
    This episode features television personality Kevin O'Connor. Topics discussed include music and the New York lottery.
  - January 6, 2001 - Part 2, cuid43590 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0292)
    Duration: 68 minutes
    Topics in this episode include the announcement of the New York lottery winner.
  - No Air Date, cuid44933
    - Adrian Flannelly and B. Maxwell, undated; cuid43552
      Duration: 22 minutes
    - Adrian Flannelly Interview, undated; cuid43554
      Duration: 33 min.
    - Adrian Flannelly and J. Roach (Ancient Order of Hibernians), undated; cuid43553
      Duration: 22 min.
    - Anglo-Irish Agreement Updates - Interview with Garret FitzGerald, undated; cuid43608
      Duration: 15 minutes
      This episode features former Taoiseach Garret Fitzgerald. Topics discussed include the Anglo-Irish Agreement updates.
    - Demo Tape of The Adrian Flannelly Show, undated; cuid43596
      Duration: 85 min.
    - Discussion on Tourism Taxation, undated; cuid43600
      This episode features Irish radio and television presenter Gay Byrne. Topics discussed include tourism taxation.
    - Excerpt Mayor of Derry, undated; cuid43598
      This episode features musician Mickey Carton.
    - Industrial Development Authority (IDA) Ireland, undated; cuid43622
      Duration: 10 minutes
      This episode features the Director of North America for Industrial Development Authority (IDA) Ireland. Topics discussed include enterprise development.
    - Interview with Consulate General of Ireland, Daithí Ó Ceallaigh, undated; cuid43623
      This episode features the Consulate General of Ireland Daithí Ó Ceallaigh. It also includes a message from the President of Ireland.
    - Interview with the Director of Patrick MacGill Summer School, undated; cuid43611
      Duration: 27 minutes
      This episode features the Patrick MacGill Summer School Director.
    - Interviews with Patrick Peyton and John Murphy from the Irish Voice, undated; cuid43594
      Duration: 54 minutes
      This episode features Brian Murphy, Patrick Peyton, and John Murphy from the Irish Voice.
    - Irish Immigration Reform Meeting, undated; cuid43613
      Duration: 20 minutes
      Topics discussed in this episode include support for Irish immigrants, employment issues, and a general report on the Inaugural Meeting of the Irish Immigration Reform Movement.
    - Noon, undated; cuid43606
      Duration: 72 min.
    - Tourism Discount Information for Dublin and Irish Cultural Sharing., undated; cuid43604
      Duration: 17 minutes
      This episode features J. Bastable and An Hengas. Topics discussed include tourism discount information for Dublin and Irish cultural sharing.
- Series II: Additional Tapes, 1983-2000; 31 audiocassettes in a flat box
  This series contains 31 audiocassettes donated by Flannelly whose association with his radio program is unclear. These recordings include sound checks, event coverage, interviews, religious recordings, and music.
  - Sound Check with Trish, March 1983; cuid43561 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0263)
    Duration: 33 minutes
    This recording contains a sound check conducted by Trish.
  - Ballyshannon - Live Report, 1984; cuid43562
    This episode was recorded on location as part of a live report of the Ballyshannon Folk and Traditional Music Festival in Co. Donegal in Ireland.
  - Malachy - Live Report with Trish, May 1986; cuid43572 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0274)
    Duration: 33 min
  - Gay McIntyre - Live Music Show, October 30, 1988; cuid43582
    Duration: 87 min.
  - Religious service, January 1989; cuid43583
    Duration: 30 min.
  - Subway Series Coverage / Irish Business Organization Event Report and Interview, October 21, 2000; cuid43585 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0287)
    Duration: 120 min
    Topics discussed in this episode include the World Series between the New York Mets and New York Yankees (also known as the "Subway Series") and the Irish Business Organization Event report.
  - Adrian on Local Radio - Ballina, undated; cuid43592
  - Barry Moore, undated; cuid43593
    Duration: 62 min.
    This episode features Barry Moore and includes a live music performance of "Mothers of the Disappeared."
  - Catholic Charities, undated; cuid43595
    Duration: 3 minutes
    Topics discussed in the episode include New York Catholic Charities supporting hospitals, maternity centers, and social service offices.
  - Children's School Music Festival and Music, undated; cuid43607
    This episode features a children's school music festival and live music.
  - Dukakis and Irish American Forum, undated; cuid43597
    Topics discussed in this episode include the Irish American Forum on peace, justice, diplomacy, economy, and progress in immigration.
  - Interview about Politics & Recent Elections in Ireland, undated; cuid43614
    Duration: 46 minutes
    This episode features Emer Hagee. Topics discussed include politics and the recent elections in Ireland.
  - Irish Racing Event Report, undated; cuid43621
    This tape features a live report of an Irish Racing Event including: music performances, conversations, and interviews.
  - Music Performances -- Glen Miller, George Gershwin, and Linda Ronstadt, undated; cuid43601
    This episode features discussions about Glen Miller, George Gershwin, and Linda Ronstadt. The episode also includes music performances.
  - New York Newsday Weather Service Call Recording, undated; cuid43619
    Duration: 3 minutes; Preservation Note: Low Volume
    This tape features a recording of a New York Newsday Weather Service Call.
  - North Kingston Event and Interviews, undated; cuid43620
    This tape features a live report and interview from the North Kingston Tribute Event.
  - Political Dialogue Conference and Panel Recording, undated; cuid43616
    Duration: 51 minutes
    The tape features a live recording of a panel - speakers unidentified.
  - "The Rambling House" - Folk Irish Music Performance, undated; cuid43599
    This episode includes a folk music performance about a Dublin farmer and the hardships they endure. This episode also includes an extract from "The Rambling House."
  - Ruthie Morrissey - Irish Soldier Boys, undated; cuid43609
    Duration: 61 min.
  - Simple Mix Gold Dream Music, undated; cuid43610
    This recording contains music only.
  - Speech from Charles Haughey, undated; cuid43602
  - Speech about Legal Immigration, undated; cuid43605
    Duration: 45 minutes
    This episode features Kennedy Hearings speech on legal immigration. Topics discussed include a review of the registration processes to uphold core principles.
  - Speeches about Ireland, Fianna Fáil, and U.S. Relations, undated; cuid43603
    This episode features Councilor Joe Malone of Fianna Fáil discussing Ireland-U.S. relations.
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade, undated; cuid43625
    Duration: 2 minutes
    This tape features and interview with Governor Mario Cuomo at a St. Patricks Day Parade.
  - Unidentified Music, undated; cuid43615
    This tape contains music only.
  - Unidentified Music, undated; cuid43617
    Duration: 16 minutes
    This tape contains only music.
  - Unidentified Music, undated; cuid43618
  - Unidentified Music, undated; cuid43624
  - Unidentified Music, undated; cuid43627
    Duration: 38 minutes
  - Unidentified Musical Performance, undated; cuid43626
    Duration: 72 minutes
    This tape features a live music performance event.